Stefani Sanchez

Seattle, WA | (509) 945 - 7986 | <u>stefanimsanchez@gmail.com</u> <u>stefanisanchez.com</u> | <u>linkedin.com/in/stefanisanchez</u> | <u>github.com/stefanisanchez</u>

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Data Analyst with experience in strategic data analysis, user interface & experience, and marketing & storytelling. **Technical Skills**: Google Analytics, MS Excel, Sublime Text, VS Code, ChatGPT, R, Java, SQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, PHP, TypeScript, GitHub, Version Control

Design Skills: Adobe Software Programs (InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop, XD), Canva, Sketch, Invision

EDUCATION

University of Washington | Seattle, WA

09/2015 - 06/2019

- Bachelor of Science in Informatics, Bachelor of Science in Speech and Hearing Sciences

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer/Designer Independent Contractor | Seattle, WA

11/2022 - Present

- Collaborated with cross-functional teams, including project managers and consultants, to ensure the successful implementation of web solutions that met client's specific needs and aligned with solution architectures

Web Developer 07/2021 – 10/2022

Envirolssues | Seattle, WA

- Transformed raw data into compelling insights that steered strategic direction

- Worked with stakeholders to research and document business, technical, and analytical requirements
- Crafted intuitive reports and visualizations

Administrative Specialist II

09/2019 - 07/2021

Cancer Research And Biostatistics (CRAB) | Seattle, WA

- Performed ad-hoc data analysis, data entry, and data cleaning
- Shared company story and expertise through social media posts and blog posts
- Dove deep into services, platforms, and tools to deliver transformative recommendations based on my findings

Software Engineer Intern OMNI ePartners | Seattle, WA

06/2018 - 08/2019

- Wove compelling narratives from diverse datasets
- Documented and refined internal development processes
- Analyzed user behavior to improve website experience

PROJECTS

Mobile App Design Project – Spring OS

01/2019 - 03/2019

University of Washington Information School | Seattle, WA

- Collaborated with team of designers to contribute design insights and ensure a holistic solution that satisfied project requirements
- Applied user-centered design principles to create intuitive and user-friendly applications
- Analyzed project requirements to understand user needs and integrate them into the design process for successful implementation

Client - Side Development Project - Food Manager App University of Washington Information School | Seattle, WA

09/2018 - 12/2018

- Applied experience with responsive design to optimize layouts for various devices and screen sizes
- Styled the appearance of the web pages to create a responsive, usable, and engaging experience for users
- Produced a standards-compliant and universally accessible website using React